zeibiz.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**Use of Cookies**

This website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.

You can accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, by doing this, you may not be able to fully utilize the features of our website.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, We use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe our posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), We ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We work with advertising companies such as Google Adsense, Amazon and Content.ad. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.
